Masshiro na keshiki ni ima sasowarete
Boku wa yuku yo mada minu sekai e
Woah
Maigo no mama tabi shiteita
nezumiiro no sora no shita
Higawari no chizu
ikutsumo no yume ga nijinde ita
Itsuka wa sa chippoke na
boku no kono hohaba demo
Ano kumo no mukou made yukeru kana
Tsuyogatte kizutsuita kokoro sukashita you ni
Furidashita amatsubutachi ga
ranhansha kurikaesu
Massugu na hikari ga kousa shite
Yukusaki mo tsugenu mama
dokomademo tsukinukeru
Awai zanzou ryoume ni yakistukete
Kono sora no shita donna toko ni ite mo
Todoku hazu nanda mada minu sekai e
Hello? Can anyone hear me?
Hello? Anybody?!
Dammit.
It's Ling's fault! That idiot prince!
Who do you think you are to call me that?
Huh?
Ling!
You can't call the future
emperor of a nation an idiot!
Are you alright?
Hold on.
What's wrong?
How do I know you're not Envy in disguise?
Oh, come on.
Do you want me to recite the hotel
room service menu from top to bottom?
Alright, you're Ling.
And what about you?
How do I know you're not Envy?
You little runt!
Who you calling a little runt? You jerk!
Okay, it's really you.
How did we even get here?
Last thing I remember,
Gluttony swallowed us whole.
So you think this cavernous void
is the inside of Gluttony's stomach?
Most likely.
Look, there.
That's the abandoned
house where we were hiding.
Also, check this out..
And that's the Lieutenant's car!
And I'm guessing all the fire
is from the Colonel's attack.
Oh, yeah.
That proves it.
But how could Gluttony's
belly be this huge?
I have no idea.
But I sincerely doubt that
this is a very pleasant place.
Gimme that.
What is it?
[GASP]
Ling, look at this!
Is that Al's?
Why is it just his hand?
Maybe he didn't get swallowed.
Then he's safe.
He's gotta be freaking out,
wondering where we are now.
I wish there was some
way I could contact him.
[YODELLING SCREAM]
Conveniently awaken, telepathic powers!
Elric brother telepathy!
- Yeah, good luck with that.
- Come in, brother! Come in!
This place is like a wasteland
of buildings and human remains.
They're all from different time periods.
I'm starting to wonder if
there's even a way out of here.
If not, then I'll make us one.
You will, will you?
How and where?
Okay, now drop the torch.
Oh, I get it now.
Here goes.
[SILENCE]
We should have heard it land by now, right?
A wall! There has to be a wall!
There has to be!
No matter how huge this place is,
if we keep heading straight,
we're gonna reach the edge!
There's gotta be some
kind of exit somewhere!
I still haven't found her yet.
Where is she?
It isn't like her to just
disappear like this.
Maybe she got eaten by
a stray dog or something.
Eaten?!
- [WAILING]
- I was joking!
She's not a cat.
She's actually a panda, but
she got a disease when she was a baby
and it kept her from growing all the way.
I nursed her back to health
after her mother abandoned her.
Since then, she's been
almost like a sister to me.
My family, the Chang Clan,
is one of the lowest-ranked houses out of
the fifty clans that make up the Xing Empire.
We have little to no power at all.
[SOFT GASP]
Maybe that's why I was drawn to her.
She looked so helpless and weak,
I couldn't help but identify with her.
Hmm.
But at the time, I guess I just
took pity on her more than anything.
[MEWL]
[TINY GROWL]
Ahh!
[SOFT WHIMPERING]
But that changed,
and she became a part of my family.
We've been through so much together.
She's always been with me.
It feels so wrong not having her here now.
I don't think I could have
gone through everything I have,
without Xiao-Mei by my side.
I know for a fact that I couldn't have
made it across the desert without her.
Sure, but that was a
pointless endeavor anyway.
Why would you risk your life like that for
something as preposterous as immortality?
Because it's the last hope
that my clan has.
If I don't return with a
method for attaining immortality
and present it to the Emperor,
it's almost certain my clan will perish!
That's...why I risked my life
crossing the desert...with Xiao-Mei.
- [WAILING]
- Come on, cut it out!
You're gonna drown us all!
Sir?
We've got some time
before the sun comes up.
There won't be as many
guards patrolling the streets.
Eh?
You mean you're gonna help
me try to find her?
He's a good person.
His people were completely wiped
out during the civil war a few years ago.
That's right.
He knows a thing or two about loss.
So I'm sure he can identify with
your worries about the fate of your clan.
What's the hold up?
You coming or not?
Yeah! Let's go!
[GIGGLING]
This is really starting to get old.
Blood doesn't make for good terrain.
I noticed.
And we're still not any closer to an exit.
I'm starving to death.
As soon as we're out,
I'll let you order anything from room service.
You can eat as much as you
want, and sleep as long as you like.
Ling?
I can't make it.
Don't tell me...
you're giving up so soon?
Are you that pathetic?
It's bad enough when you collapse
in the street, but here? Get up!
Come on!
Quit being so weak!
Just go.
You spineless jellyfish!
All right, fine then!
Give up and die if you want,
but you're not dragging me down.
I'm seriously leaving you here!
I'm not messing around, Ling!
[GROANING]
I thought you were gonna leave me behind.
There's way too many people
I'd be letting down by dying here.
And you've got people waiting
for you to get back too, right?
So shut up!
If you're strong enough to—
[YELPS]
So hungry.
I wish we could find something to eat.
[PANTING]
Well, actually, you know...
Leather goods are edible.
We've got a meal.
That should do it.
Here you go.
You don't have athlete's foot, do you?
My foot is made of metal, you idiot!
Ohh, man.
That shoe filled me up.
I'm sorry, Ed.
And why is that?
It's all my fault that you're here.
It is not.
Besides, this place is a joke compared
to what my teachers put me through.
It just sucks that we have
no idea where this place is.
But that's all right.
As long as we've got our health,
we can find an exit outta here.
You're sure optimistic.
Not really. I'm just stubborn.
And if I even think about giving up,
I have Al's iron fist to look forward to.
Huh...
What's wrong?
There's something out there.
Is that...?
I thought so.
I should've known it'd be you guys.
It's definitely Envy.
- Please show me the way outta here!
- [LING GASPS]
You're just going to start begging
the enemy for help like that?
If it means surviving,
I'll be his best friend!
- Talk about a sellout!
- It doesn't matter because there is no exit.
[GASPS]
You've really gotten us into a fine mess.
I can't believe you got me
swallowed with you.
You just said swallowed.
So we really are inside Gluttony's stomach?
Well, yes and no.
See, it's a lot more complicated than that.
Just ask the pip—
I mean the alchemist.
He should've realized what place this is.
I did notice something
when Gluttony swallowed us.
It was like I had a familiar feeling.
So you do remember then.
This isn't the first time
you've been through this.
[GASP]
- Portal of truth!
- [GASP]
But...
But it wasn't pitch black
and filled with a sea of blood.
It was more like...
Like an entirely white void.
Oh yeah?
So that's what the real one looks like.
The real one?
Gluttony is a failed experiment by
our father to create his own portal of truth.
He's... a what?
Despite how powerful our father is,
he still couldn't create one.
We're trapped inside a
defective portal of truth.
So this place, it exists somewhere
in between reality and truth.
In between?
And I can assure you that
there's no way out of here.
The only option we've got is to
sit here until our strength runs out.
And that's it.
All we can do is wait here to die.
Fullmetal Alchemist.
No way... Don't think I'm
falling for any of that crap!
I know you're lying to us, Envy!
You're lying, aren't you?!
So there really isn't a way out?
We're gonna die here?
Wait... No... Hold on...
I can't die here...
What's Al gonna do if I die?
We made a promise, and he...
He needs me to get back to normal.
Dammit!
I wanna know who your father is!
Who would try to create their own portal?!
It's Führer Bradley, isn't it?!
[SCOFFs]
What, are you serious?
Huh, nice try, but King Bradley's
nothing more than a Homunculus.
[GASP]
Told you so.
The Fifth Laboratory...
Human lives sacrificed to make Philosopher's Stones...
Homunculi...
And if the Führer's on your side,
then I'm guessing you're the ones behind Ishval.
Oh, Ishval!
[CACKLING] I couldn't have asked for a
more enjoyable job than that.
You remember the incident
that started the war, right?
[GASP]
I had always heard it was because a military
officer accidentally shot an Ishvalan child.
Yep.
And the one that proudly pulled
the trigger was none other than yours truly.
[GASP]
Excuse me.
I know what happened in Ishval.
Yoki told me.
You have no idea how good that felt.
I ravaged their entire
country with a single bullet.
[LAUGHS]
I mean, talk about invigorating!
Oh, and the best part?
The officer that I pretended to be?
He was actually a moderate who would always
publicly oppose the military's occupation in Ishval.
And listen to this?
The poor fool couldn't come up with a plausible
defense and they court-martialled him!
You know, I don't think I'll ever get over
how easily manipulated humans are.
[CACKLING]
So you're responsible.
You were the one who shot
and killed that poor innocent child.
You destroyed my hometown.
You drove out the Ishvalans.
You're the one who turned
Scar into a murderer.
And it was you.
You're the reason
Winry's parents were killed!
You're the one to blame!
What the hell?
He didn't budge.
Okay, then. If that's how you want it.
Ed, get back!
I'm gonna show you two boys
something neat before we die.
Consider it a parting gift!
Did you notice his footprints back
when we were all fighting in the forest?
What? No.
What's your point?
Just that he's freakishly
heavy for the size of his body.
He might be a bit bigger than he looks.
Damn!
What the hell?
How is that a Homunculus?!
They're supposed to be artificial humans, right?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
What should... What do I do?
I have no idea.
Hmm...
What do I do?
I'm scared.
I don't want Father to be mad at me.
Huh...
What did you say?
You have a father?
Uh-huh.
Is he the one that made the Homunculi?
Father made us.
[GASP]
Where does everything he swallows go?
It's gotta be some kind of trick.
Come on, think!
We made a promise and
Brother might still be alive!
I can't just give up now!
Gluttony...
Will you take me with you?
Will you take me to meet your father?
I guess so.
[GASP]
He'll be happy since
you're a human sacrifice.
Uh—
Oh, sure, right!
That's why he'll wanna meet me!
And I guess I'll find out...
what that means.
In regards to the search
for potential sacrifices,
our only candidates
are the Elric brothers.
What about Dr. Marcoh?
Isn't he ready?
We still have Kimblee.
I doubt that Kimblee could muster up
the nerve it takes to open the portal.
That reminds me.
How have things been progressing
along with Mustang's candidacy?
That's a question for the Fuhrer.
He plans on having a
nice long talk with him.
Tell me, why are you
bothering to let me live?
Because you aren't going to learn
your lesson if you're dead, soldier.
And the military?
How long has all this been going on?
The Homunculi have been controlling
this entire nation since its inception.
So all this time you've been sitting
back and laughing at our struggles?
I saw you at General Hughes' funeral.
Your hands were trembling.
So did you fake that as well?
Why must everyone make such a
fuss over the death of a single soldier?
The moment a soldier dons his uniform,
he accepts the reality that he might be buried in it.
And about my hands,
Hughes' child screeched throughout
the entirety of his funeral.
My hands were trembling with anger.
How can you even say such a thing?
You have a child too.
You're speaking of Selim?
He's more well behaved than that.
And how do you think he'd react if he
found out that his father was a Homunculus?
Was that a threat?
You'll have to do better.
Selim will never work as a
point of weakness in my life.
But you on the other hand...
I know exactly who to use as your weak point.
Lieutenant Hawkeye!
What's wrong, Sergeant?
I received a memo from
the Personnel Bureau.
And, well, I'm being transferred
to the Southern Command Center.
They transferred you?!
And I'm not the only one.
Breda's being sent to the Western Command.
And Warrant Officer Falman's been
reassigned to the Northern Command.
[GASP]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Lieutenant Hawkeye?
Yes, sir.
I'm Yakovlev from Personnel.
Am I being transferred?
And my name is Storche.
I'm the personal assistant to Fuhrer Bradley.
I need you to take this.
Am I being reassigned, sir?
That's correct.
I'd like to look at them.
What is this?!
This can't be right!
Are you sure that these are my orders?
Where are they sending you?
First Lieutenant Riza Hawkeye is to
report for duty at Central Command Center...
[RELIEVED EXHALE]
As personal assistant to Fuhrer Bradley.
[GASPS]
It's as simple as that.
She'll be under my watch from now on.
[DISTORTED VOICES]
Play with me! Let's play!
Hell no! You go and play by yourself!
Uh...this isn't good!
[DISTORTED LAUGHTER]
Ah!
Ling!
[DISTORTED CACKLE]
Ed!
Can you make a weapon?
You got it!
With this ocean of blood,
there's plenty of iron to work with!
You have the tackiest sense of taste.
Aw, come on!
I think it looks pretty damn sharp, myself!
[DISTORTED LAUGHTER]
Can we take him?
I doubt it. He is a giant monster.
And then on top of that,
I'm pretty sure he broke two of my ribs.
Yeah, I'm pretty beat up myself.
But that's beside the point.
All that matters now is
filling him with some pain!
Are you sure this is
the right way, Gluttony?
Uh-huh!
But this is the way...it can't be....
Your father is living in Central?
Let it all out, let it all out
Tsuyogaranakute ii n da ne
Dareka ga kaite'tta
Kabe no rakugaki no hana ga yureru
Jibunrashisa nante, dare mo wakaranai yo
Nagai nagai michi no tochuu
de nakushitari, hirottari,
Kyuu ni samishiku natte,
naichau hi mo aru kedo
Namida mo itami mo, hoshi ni kaeyou
Ashita wo terasu akari wo tomosou
Chiisana te kazashite
futari de tsukurou hoshikuzu wo
Tsuyoku hikaru ein wo
Sayonara itsuka wa kuru ka mo shirenu
Kisetsu wa sore demo meguri megutte'ku
Chiisaku mayotte mo aruite'ku
Kimi to aruite'ku
Sore daku wa kawaranaide iyou ne
The lost souls of the forgotten past litter
the path leading toward the unknown future.
The young man knows he must fight...
But the only way for him to discover the truth
is to fully explore the darkness that engulfs it.
Next time on Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood
Episode 26: Reunion
I refuse to say goodbye when I'm certain
that our paths will cross once again in the future.